http://www.airelectro.com/privacy/

Excellence in the Distribution, Assembly and Manufacturing of Electrical Connector, Contacts and Related Accessories.
ADI Electronics
MIL-DTL-24308 Connectors with Solder, Crimp, and Printed Circuit Contacts.
AEI Manufacturing
Custom Contacts & Connectors Equivalent to: MIL-DTL 38999 Series I, II, III, MIL-DTL 26482 Series I, II, ARINC 400, ARINC 600, Custom Printed Circuit Contacts, Cable Assembly, Kitting, Application Engineering, Custom Backshells & Accessories.
Amphenol Pcd
MIL-T-81714 Series I & III, Audio Connectors MIL-C-55116, Power Connectors MIL-DTL-55181, APeX Galley Connectors (ARINC 810), 62GB & 162GB Series, AS85049 Back-shells, Luminus Series, (535) Pegasus Series, Relay Sockets (M12883), MIL-DTL 24308, Junction Modules, Terminal Blocks, Ground Blocks.
Arizona Connector and Design
Wire wrap contacts, connectors, surface mount technology, adapters, bonding jumpers, right angle contacts for ARINC 600 style connectors and discontinued interconnect products.
Arizona Electrical Products
Galley Connectors, High Reliable Contacts for Mil Spec Connectors, D38999 PC Tail Pins and Sockets, Coax, Triax and Quadrax Contacts.
Carlisle Jerrik, ECS
EMI filter and transient suppression connectors.
Carlisle - Tri-Star Electronics
MIL-AS 39029 and Proprietary Contacts, Crimp, Solder, Printed Circuit, Wire Wrap®, Thermocouple, Coaxial.
Corsair
MIL-DTL 5010 Rear ReleaseMIL-DTL 26482 Series IIAircraft External Power Receptacles.
Filconn
Filtered, EMP Protected & Specialty Interconnect Products for Customers in the Aerospace, Military, and Medical Markets. FilConn, Inc. offers key technologies for use in mil-aerospace connector applications. The most common of these technologies is capacitive filtering.
Glenair
MIL-AS 80549 and Proprietary Accessories, Dust Caps, Plastic and Metal Conduit, Composite Accessories, Backshells and Termini, MIL-AS 83513 & Custom Micro-D Connectors, Hermetic 38999 Connectors, Series 80 "Mighty Mouse" Connectors, Harsh Environment Connectors.
Positronic
MIL-DTL-24308 (M24308), MIL-C-39029 (M39029), MIL-PRF-28748 (M28748), GFSC S-311, IEC 60807, IP65, IP67, PICMG 2.11, PICMG 3.8, CompactPCI, AdvancedTCA, MicroTCA, VITA 41, ARINC 801, RoHS, REACH, ITAR, UL, CUL, CSA, TUV, ISO9001, and AS9100 among others.
Radiall
Multi-contact Rectangular Connectors, ARINC 404, ARINC 600, MIL-DTL 81659, MIL-DTL 83527, MIL-DTL 39029, BPX, DSX, MPX, NSX, EPX®, EPXB®, BACC47, BACC 65, BACC66.
RMS
MIL-DTL 26500 Class R Type B, MIL-DTL 26500 Class R Type T, BACC45 and BACC63.
Souriau-Sunbank by Eaton
MIL-DTL 38999 Series I, III, 851 Series, MIL-DTL 26482 Series I, II 8525 (ASNE005) Series, 8526 Series, ELIO High Speed Fiber Optic Tech, Engine & Firewall Connectors (ASNE004, ESC, EN2997 & QPL'd), RB Series Ground Modules, Trim Trio, JBX, Push Pull.
TE Connectivity (Deutsch)
Hermetic Connectors (MIL-DTL 26482 Series II, MIL-DTL 38999, MIL-DTL 83723 Series III, MIL-DTL 81714).
Products
Connectors
MIL-DTL-38999 Connectors
Hermetic Connectors
MIL-DTL-26482 Connectors
MIL-DTL-5015 (MIL-C-5015) Connectors
MIL-DTL-26500 (MIL-C-26500)
MIL-DTL-83723 III
EN (AIRBUS) Connectors -EN3645, EN3646
Glenair Mil-DTL 83513 (Micro—D)
BACC (Boeing) Connectors
PUSH-PULL Connectors
High-Speed Connectors
Power Connectors
Circular Connectors
D-Sub Connectors
Rectangular Connectors
Contacts
Press Fit Contacts
Search:
Home
/
Privacy
Privacy Policy
Air Electro, Inc. respects your privacy and the purpose for which our site visitors provide us information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.
Information Collected
If you request or submit information to Air Electro, Inc. by sending an e-mail via the "mail to:" function or filling out a "request for information" form, we may save your e-mail address as well as any other information you may provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, e-mail, or phone to convey information about Air Electro, Inc. solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your e-mail and other information you provide will not be sold to any third party.
Information Collected by Others
This notice addresses only the policy of Air Electro, Inc. website and not the sites that users access via links from our site. Air Electro, Inc. is not responsible for the information collection policies of other sites, nor for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, nor for the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.
Cookies
The Air Electro, Inc. website does not use cookies.
Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information
If you would like to have your personal information removed from Air Electro, Inc., please send an e-mail via the feedback form, with "Remove personal information" in the subject line. To update, change, or correct your personal information, please send an e-mail via the feedback form with the appropriate changes.
Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information
Air Electro, Inc. may disclose information when legally compelled to do so; in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.
Periodic Policy Changes
Please note that Air Electro, Inc. reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.
This policy statement is made in the name of Air Electro, Inc. and is effective as of June 18, 2010. This statement does not create an agreement between Air Electro, Inc. and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.
For inquiries contact:
Air Electro, Inc.
Get Directions »
Call 1-800 458-4412 (Toll Free) or 1-818 407-5400 • Fax 1-818 407-5460
Copyright © 2020. All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy
AEI NEWS & BLOG
Rectangular Connectors: Positronic Power & Hybrid ConnectorsRectangular Connectors: Positronic Offerings
All News »
Copyright © 2020. All Rights Reserved.
Don't Miss Out!
Join our VIP list for recaps of the Feedspot Top 50 Rated Connector Corner Blog series! Plus AEI news, updates and offers.
Submit
